Carter Davis

Phone: 07500600258 Email: carterdavis1928@gmail.com

Personal Statement

After achieving high grades in Computer Science, Maths and Business I progressed onto a software and website development course at college. During my summer break, I pursued an IT support job which gave me experience in customer support and IT problem solving.

Employment History

Halesowen College (IT Technician - Fixed Term)

(July 2021 - September 2021)

- Provide IT support to staff.
- Replace computer components.
- Install operating systems.

Newsquest (Newspaper Distributor)

(August 2018 - May 2020)

- Deliver newspapers weekly to 185 homes in the local area.
- Prepare newspapers and their accompanying leaflets.

Education

Sandwell Academy

(September 2015 - July 2020)

- 9 GCSEs including a 9 in Computer Science, 7 in Maths and a 4 in English.
- 1 BTEC Level 2 Distinction in Business.

Halesowen College

(September 2020 - Present)

• Software and Website Development - Level 3

Key Skills

- Customer support
- C#, Shell, Python
- Problem solving

Hobbies & Interests

I take interest in amateur radio and am currently a committee member in the Midlands Amateur Radio Society where I aim to bring a younger audience to amateur radio.